decluttr.com 2018-01-07

# Information Collected | Privacy Policy | Decluttr

**Collection of Personal Information**  
Decluttr collects personal information provided by you when you register for an account with us, complete a survey, and/or when you contact us to inquire about our products or services. When you provide personal information through our Website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

The personal information we collect may include the following: Name, home address, email address, your home and/or mobile phone numbers, your gender, and your date of birth.  

We may collect additional personal information in connection with your participation in any promotions offered by us.

**Collection of Non-Personal Information**  
We may automatically collect non-personal information about visitors to our Website, such as number of visitors, Internet Protocol address, browser type, operating system and pages viewed, but we will not combine such data with any personal information. We use this data in the aggregate to determine how visitors use our Website so we can improve your experience on our Website. We also collect information about your transactions with us.

We may use “cookies” (text files placed on your computer by a web page server) or other technologies (such as web beacons and pixel tags) to collect such non-personal information. Decluttr uses cookies for a number of purposes, for instance to enable us to simplify the logging on process for registered users, to help ensure the security and authenticity of registered users, to provide the mechanisms for online shopping and to enable traffic monitoring. 

Non-registered visitors to the Website are sent anonymous cookies to keep track of their browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. In addition, any visitor who has clicked on a Decluttr.com advertisement on another site that links to Decluttr.com will be sent anonymous cookies that will allow us to analyze advertising effectiveness and manage our relationship with affiliate sites.

You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser on your computer.  If you refuse cookies, however, certain functions and conveniences of the Website may not work properly. For example, if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to complete a transaction through our Website.

Additionally, when you download or use Decluttr mobile applications, we may collect and process information about your actual location and your mobile device, including a unique device identifier. We may use this information to provide you with location-based products and services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off or opt out of location-based services.
